RG 097, Connecticut Commission on the Arts
Connecticut State Library
- Series 2. Dance, 1965-1977
  - National Dance Companies (Box 49)
    - New York City Ballet (Box 52)
    - The Solomon’s Dance Company - Dance Theatre Foundation Inc. (Box 53)
    - Stagium Chamber Ballet (Brazilian) (Box 53)
    - State Ballet Company (Charleston, S.C.) (Box 53)
    - St. Mark’s Dance Company (Washington D.C.) (Box 53)
    - Story Time Dance Theatre (New Jersey) (Box 53)
    - Sung Hae Oh (New York) (Box 53)
    - Susana y Jose (Box 53)
    - Miss Hahomi Tachibana (New York) (Box 53)
    - Tance and Trio (California) (Box 53)
    - Paul Taylor Dance Company (New York) (Box 53)
    - The Glen Tetley Dance Company (Box 53)
    - Twyla Tharpe and Dancers (Box 53)
    - Theatre Flamenco of San Fransisco (California) (Box 53)
    - Clive Thompson (Box 53)
    - Tokunage Dance Company (Box 53)
    - Joyce Trisler - The Danscompany (Box 53)
    - Utah Repertory Dance Theatre (Box 53)
    - Jan Veen Theatre of the Dance, Inc. (Massachusetts) (Box 53)
    - Dan Wagonner and Dancers (Box 53)
    - Ruth Walton (New York) (Box 53)
    - Miyoko Watanabe (New York) (Box 53)
    - Norman Walker Dance Company (Box 53)
    - Washington Dance Theatre (Box 53)
    - Weidman, Charles and his Theatre Dance Company (Box 53)
    - The Anne Wilson Dance Company (New York) (Box 53)
    - Ethel Winter Dance Company (New York) (Box 53)
    - The Wisconsin Ballet Company (Box 53)
    - Jan Wodynska Dance Company (Box 53)
    - Young American dance Company (New York) (Box 53)
    - Yuriko and Dance Company (Box 53)
    - Gerda Zimmerman (Box 53)
    - San Fransisco Ballet (Box 53)
    - San Fransisco Dance Theatre (Box 53)
    - Sasha - Dances of India (Box 53)
    - Triveni Kala Sangam Dance of Manipur (Box 53)
    - Ramon Segarra (New York) (Box 53)
    - Shala and Raja (New York) (Box 53)
    - Uday Shankar (Box 53)
    - Anna Sokolow Dance Company (New York) (Box 53)
    - Mick Sgroi (Box 53)
  - Dance Component, 1968-1975 (Box 54)
    - Fiscal Reports - Dance Touring Program, 1968-1974 (Box 54)
    - Dance Touring Program - Applicants, 1978 (Box 54)
    - NEA Dance Touring Program FY1977. FY1978 (Box 54)
    - Dance Touring Program - Bob Moon’s Proposal, 1975 (Box 54)
    - Touring - General (Box 54)
    - Touring - (New England, etc.) (Box 54)
    - Touring - Statistics, 1975 (Box 54)
    - NEA Dance Touring. American Dance Festival, 1976 (Box 54)
    - Dance Touring Program Wesleyan (The Open Eye), 1976 (Box 54)
    - The Dance Touring Program, 1976 (Box 54)
    - Dance Touring Program, Bushnell Auditorium, 1976 (Box 54)
    - Dance Touring Program, University of Connecticut, 1976 (Box 54)
    - NEA Dance Touring Program: Correspondence, Reports, 1975 (Box 54)
    - Dance Touring Program (74-75) Wesleyan and Wadsworth (Sponsors), 1974-1975 (Box 54)
    - Dance Touring Program: Evaluations (Box 54)
    - Dance Touring Program American Dance Festival, 1974-1975 (Box 54)
    - Dance Touring Program University of Connecticut (Jorgensen) Jack Cohan, 1974-1975 (Box 54)
    - Dance Touring Program Bushnell (Graham - Joffrey II), 1974-1975 (Box 54)
    - NEA Dance Touring Program Evaluation Forms, 1975 (Box 54)
    - Education - Option B Application, 1978 (Box 54)
    - AIS Application FY1977 (Box 54)
    - AIS Dance (Box 54)
    - NEA Artists - In - Schools (Dance Component) - Guidelines, 1977 (Box 54)
    - NEA AIS (Dance Component) Applications, forms, etc., 1976-1977 (Box 54)
    - NEA AIS (Dance Component) Applications, Program Description, Evaluation, 1975-1976 (Box 54)
    - NEA AIS (Dance) Evaluation, 1975 (Box 54)
    - NEA AIS Program, Dance Component Guide, 1974-1975 (Box 54)
    - NEA AIS (Dance), 1975-1976 (Box 54)
    - NEA AIS (Dance) Evaluations, 1976 (Box 54)
    - NEA AIS Dance, 1974-1975 (Box 54)
    - NEA AIS Dance Component - Applications, 1975-1976 (Box 54)
    - AIS Dance Litchfield Junior and Senior High Joseph Berube, Principal, 1974-1975 (Box 54)
    - NEA Dance Program Guidelines, 1975 (Box 54)
  - Movement Companies (Box 54)
    - Evaluations - Movement Workshops (Box 54)
    - Original Comments - Movement and the Child Workshop, 1970 March 8 (Box 54)
    - Original Comments - Movement for the Dancer Workshops I and II, 1968 March-April (Box 54)
    - Original Evaluation - Movement and the Adolescent Workshop (Box 54)
    - Original Evaluation - Movement and the Child Workshop (Box 54)
    - Original Comments - Movement as Communication Workshop, 1968 May 20 (Box 54)
    - Dance Film - In Comments. Originals (Box 54)
  - Dance / Movement Workshops, 1967-1970 (Box 55)
    - Education (Box 55)
    - Education - Integrating the Arts Committee, New Haven. Confidential (Box 55)
    - Educational Arts Association (Box 55)
    - Education - Dance in Public School (Box 55)
    - Elementary School Principals Association of Connecticut Meeting (Box 55)
    - Dance Teachers Workshop Connecticut College, 1967 August (Box 55)
    - Dance Teachers Workshop Artists, 1967 August (Box 55)
    - Dance Teachers Workshop Comments From Participants, 1967 August (Box 55)
    - Dance Teachers Workshop Correspondence and List of People Who Received Copies of Evaluation, 1967 August (Box 55)
    - Dance Teachers Workshop Brochure, 1967 August (Box 55)
    - Dance Teachers Workshop Geographical Distribution of Participants - Map, 1967 August (Box 55)
    - Dance Teachers Workshop Follow- Up information sent to participants, 1967 August (Box 55)
    - Dance Teachers Workshop News Release, 1967 August (Box 55)
    - Dance Teachers Workshop Housing Details, 1967 August (Box 55)
    - Dance Teachers Workshop Loring vs. TWA, 1967 August (Box 55)
    - Dance Teachers Workshop Medical Forms, 1967 August (Box 55)
    - Dance Teachers Workshop Evaluation by Ernestine Stodelle, 1967 August (Box 55)
    - Dance Teachers Workshop Follow -up to staff from Anthony S. Keller, 1967 August (Box 55)
    - Dance Teachers Workshop Dane Magazine Article by Ernestine Stodelle, 1967 August (Box 55)
    - Dance Teachers Workshop Guest List, 1967 August (Box 55)
    - Dance Teachers Workshop Participants, 1967 August (Box 55)
    - Dance Teachers Workshop Letter Sent with the Complete Report of the Jan. 9, 1967 Hearing, 1967 August (Box 55)
    - Dance Teachers Workshop Performance Details (Tickets), 1967 August (Box 55)
    - Dance Teachers Workshop Applications, 1967 August (Box 55)
    - Dance Teachers Workshop Application that were rejected. Observers., 1967 August (Box 55)
    - Dance Teachers Workshop Announcement Letter, Application Form, Acceptance Letter, 1967 August (Box 55)
    - Visiting Artists Workshop Budget and Contract, 1967 February 7 (Box 55)
    - Movement as Communication Workshop Comments, 1968 May (Box 55)
    - Principles of Movement for the Dancer Workshop, 1968 March 3, 1968 April 28 (Box 55)
    - Principles of Movement for the Announcement and Acceptance Letters (Box 55)
    - Principles of Movement for the Articles Distributed to Participants (Box 55)
    - Principles of Movement for the Evaluations from Participants (Box 55)
    - Principles of Movement for the List of Participants (Box 55)
    - Principles of Movement for the Questions for Dr. Sweigard in Advance (Box 55)
    - Movement as Communication Workshop Articles Distributed, 1968 May (Box 55)
    - Movement as Communication Budget (Box 55)
    - Movement as Communication Mailing List (Box 55)
    - Movement as Communication Participants (Box 55)
    - Movement as Communication Bartenieff and Chase Announcement and Acceptance Letters (Box 55)
    - Movement as Communication Participants Evaluation (Box 55)
    - Learning Through Movement Title V Grant Bloomfield Schools - Bonnie Bird, 1970 (Box 55)
  - Dance / Movement Exploration, 1970-1974 (Box 56)
    - Movement and the Child Workshop, 1978 March 8 (Box 56)
      - Applications (Box 56)
      - Mailing lists (Box 56)
      - Participants (Box 56)
    - Movement and the Adolescent Workshop, 1970 May 20 (Box 56)
      - Evaluation by J. Kennedy and Valente (Box 56)
      - News Release (Box 56)
      - Comment (Box 56)
      - Announcement and Acceptance letters (Box 56)
      - Student Participants for Demonstrations (Box 56)
    - Visiting Artists Workshop, 1971 February 7 (Box 56)
      - Comments and Follow Up Letter (Box 56)
      - Announcements and Acceptance Letters (Box 56)
    - Mildred Hill Workshop, Participants, 1971 February (Box 56)
    - Visiting Artists Workshop, Report by Mildred Hill, 1971 February 7 (Box 56)
    - Knowing Children Through Movement, Connecticut College, $250, SE Conn. (Box 56)
    - Dance Arts Council, 1971 May 7 (Box 56)
    - Movement as Non-Verbal Communication Workshop, evening session, 1971 July 27 (Box 56)
      - Announcement (Box 56)
      - Follow Up Letter (Box 56)
    - Movement as Non-Verbal Communication Workshop, 1971 July 19, 30 (Box 56)
      - Announcement and Acceptance Letters (Box 56)
      - Budget and Copies of Contracts (Box 56)
      - Correspondence and Report Mailing List (Box 56)
      - Reports - White and Herzig (Box 56)
      - News Release (Box 56)
      - Feedback from Participants (Box 56)
      - Applications from Participants (Box 56)
      - Information sheet from Non-Applicants (Box 56)
      - Evening session - Feedback from Participants, 1971 July 27 (Box 56)
    - Movement Workshops (in colleges), 1971 (Box 56)
      - UCONN (Storrs), October 8, 22, November 19 (Box 56)
      - WES Conn. (Danbury), October 13, 20, 27 (Box 56)
      - So. Conn. (New Haven), October 15, November 5, 12 (Box 56)
    - Prodance Movement Workshop (Branford Record Center), 1972 June 21, 25 (Box 56)
    - Movements Committee Workshop (Box 56)
    - Connecticut Summer Institute for Movement Exploration - session I (Box 56)
    - Connecticut Summer Institute for Movement Exploration - session II (Box 56)
    - Connecticut Summer Institute for Movement Exploration - Applications, 1974 (Box 56)
    - Movement for the Classroom Workshop - Research, Documentation, Bibliography, Evaluation, 1972 July 17-28 (Box 56)
    - Movement for the Classroom, 1972 July 17-28 (Box 56)
      - Budget, Contracts, Notice of the Workshop, Applications for Participants (Box 56)
      - Marcia Siegel, Lists of Acceptances (Box 56)
    - Movement for the Classroom Workshop (June Kennedy), 1972 August 5-6 (Box 56)
    - Movement and the Child Workshop Announcement and Acceptance Letters, 1970 March 8 (Box 56)
    - Movement and the Child Workshop Articles Distributed to Participants, 1970 March 8 (Box 56)
    - Movement and the Child Workshop Artists, 1970 March 8 (Box 56)
    - Movement and the Child Workshop Evaluation by Ernestine Stodelle, 1970 March 8 (Box 56)
    - Movement and the Child Workshop Map of Southern Conn. State College, 1970 March 8 (Box 56)
    - Movement and the Child Workshop Southern Conn. State College, 1970 March 8 (Box 56)
    - Movement and the Child Workshop Teacher Training Workshop 3/1/70 Conducted by Virginia Tanner, 1970 March 8 (Box 56)
    - Movement and the Child Workshop News Release, 1970 March 8 (Box 56)
    - Movement and the Child Workshop Photo Layout for Flyer, 1970 March 8 (Box 56)
    - Movement and the Adolescent University of Hartford, 1970 June 20 (Box 56)
  - Dance Touring (Box 57)
    - Young Artist’s Collaborative (Box 57)
    - Correspondence - State Arts Commissions (Box 57)
    - Evaluations - Connecticut Dance Companies (Box 57)
    - Address Lists (Box 57)
    - Incorporation Procedures (Box 57)
    - Dancer’s Contract (copy) (Box 57)
    - Neighborhood Arts (Box 57)
    - Neighborhood Arts (Box 57)
    - Effort –Shape Course (Box 57)
    - NEA Dance Touring Program UCONN Jorgenson Theatre, 1978 (Box 57)
    - NEA Dance Touring Program American Dance Festival, 1978 (Box 57)
    - NEA Dance Touring Program Hartford Ballet (Ailey, Pittsburg), 1978 (Box 57)
    - Dance Touring Program, 1977 (Box 57)
    - Challenge Grant - Artists Collective / Hartford Arts Council (Box 57)
    - Arts / Education Joint Committee (Box 57)
    - Performance Audit, April 4-5 (Box 57)
    - Policy Statements, Rules of Procedure (Box 57)
    - Theatre Project (Box 57)
    - Arts Organizations - Correspondence (Box 57)
    - ACA Reports, Notices, etc. (Box 57)
    - American Dance Guild Correspondence (Box 57)
    - Berkshire Hills Music and Dance Association (Box 57)
    - Arts Councils (Box 57)
    - Theatre Facilities Sheets (Box 57)
    - 6th Annual Conference of the National Council of the Arts in Education (Box 57)
    - Women in the arts (Box 57)
    - Title III (Box 57)
    - Title V (Box 57)
    - Title X information (Box 57)
    - National Ballet Companies List (Box 57)
      - Notice of the Workshop (Box 57)
      - Letters of Acceptance (Box 57)
      - Applications that were not Accepted (Box 57)
      - Budget (Box 57)
      - Evaluation and documentation (Box 57)
      - Applications from Participants (Box 57)
      - Contracts (Box 57)
      - Correspondence, Biography, Pictures (Box 57)
    - Movement as Non-Verbal Communication - Follow up sessions, 1971-1972 (Box 57)
    - Movement for the Classroom Workshop, 1972 July 17-28 (Box 57)
      - Biographies, Pictures of Artists (Box 57)
    - Movement Workshops (Prodance), 1972 (Box 57)
      - 1. Introductory Workshops (Box 57)
      - 2. Refresher Workshops (Box 57)
      - 3. In-Service Workshops (Box 57)
    - Connecticut Summer Institute for Movement Exploration (Quinnipiac college), 1973 July 23-1973 August 3 (Box 57)
    - Evaluations - Quinnipiac Movement Institute, session II (Box 57)
    - Connecticut Summer Institute for Movement Exploration (Quinnipiac College, 8/6/73 - 8/17/73), 1973 August 6-17 (Box 57)
    - Quinnipiac College - Video Taping Connecticut Summer Institute for Movement Exploration (Box 57)
    - Connecticut Summer Institute for Movement Exploration, session III, 1974 (Box 57)
    - Connecticut Summer Institute for Movement Exploration, session I, 1974 (Box 57)
    - Connecticut Summer Institute for Movement Exploration, Bibliography and Syllabus, 1974 (Box 57)
    - Movement Education - Development of Credit Courses in state colleges (Box 57)
    - Evaluations - J. Weiner Workshop summer, 1974 (Box 57)
    - Evaluations - B. Sommer Workshop summer, 1974 (Box 57)
    - Evaluations - D. Vislocky Workshop summer, 1974 (Box 57)
    - Eastern Connecticut state College Movement Workshops, 1974-1975 (Box 57)
    - Connecticut Summer Institute for Movement Exploration (Quinnipiac), 1974 (Box 57)
    - Questionnaire - General - All Participants in Workshops (Box 57)
- Series 3. Bicentennial Materials, 1974-1976
  - Bicentennial Planning Memoranda and Operation Jack Point (Box 16)
  - Bicentennial Humanities /Arts Joint Project (Public Architecture) (Box 16)
  - Bicentennial Other Connecticut State Agencies (Box 16)
  - Connecticut Bicentennial Program (Box 16)
  - Connecticut Local Bicentennial Committee (Box 16)
  - National Bicentennial A.R.B.A. (Box 16)
  - N.E.A. Bicentennial Program (Box 16)
  - Bicentennial - Other States (Box 16)
  - Commission Bicentennial Plans - Extra Copies (Box 16)
  - Commission Bicentennial - Planning (Box 16)
  - Bicentennial - Idea Sheet #1 (Box 16)
  - The C.C.A. logo and Bicentennial Idea Sheet (Box 16)
  - Connecticut Building types - Prop. Publ. (Box 16)
  - Bicentennial Program (Projection) (Box 16)
  - 1976 Planning (Box 16)
  - Bicentennial Ideas and Proposals (Box 16)
  - Bicentennial Ideas and Proposals (Box 16)
  - Development of a Publishing Assoc. for the Connecticut Commission on the Arts (Box 16)
  - Bicentennial Planning Memorandum #3 and Correspondence (Box 16)
  - Bicentennial Times (Box 16)
  - Seminars, A.C.A. (Box 16)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 16)
  - Bicentennial Planning Memorandum #9 (Box 16)
  - Bicentennial Idea Sheet (Box 16)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 16)
- Series 4. Project Create, 1967-1970
  - Create Evaluation (Box 17)
    - Budget - Record Book (Box 17)
    - Create Account Sheets, 1968-1969 (Box 17)
    - Linda Seagrave, Assoc. Evaluation (Box 17)
    - Evaluation Report, 1967-1968 (Box 17)
    - Evaluation - Letters of Reaction (Box 17)
    - Edward J. P. O’Connor, Proj. Evaluator (Box 17)
    - Evaluation (Box 17)
    - Evaluation - Testing (Box 17)
    - S.R.A. Examiner Manual - What I Like to Do (Box 17)
  - Create (Box 18)
    - Baldwin School (Box 18)
    - Cornwall Consolidated School (Box 18)
    - The Rectory School, Pomfret (Box 18)
    - Hide and Seek Odyssey of Madeline Gimple (Box 18)
    - Theatre at Waterford (Box 18)
    - National Theatre of the Deaf - NTD (Box 18)
    - Hartford Conservatory (Box 18)
    - The Creative Outlook - Originals (Box 18)
    - Historical Piece Written at the Beginning of 3rd Year (Box 18)
    - General Info Re Dissemination (Box 18)
    - Abstract and Brochure (Box 18)
    - Accent of Connecticut Article (Box 18)
    - Bradley Field Exhibit (Box 18)
    - Project School Staff, 1969-1970 (Box 18)
    - Planning Board Members (Box 18)
    - Coordinators Questionnaire (Box 18)
    - Enrollment figures - 9 Project School - Staff Address List (Box 18)
    - “The First Year” - Shirley Kaplan film strip dissemination (Box 18)
    - Guests at Schools for Performances (Box 18)
    - Personal Appearances (Box 18)
    - Project Application and Dissemination Correspondence (Box 18)
    - Application for Continuation, 1969-1970 (Box 18)
    - New Brochure, 1969-1970 (Box 18)
    - Richard Welling - TV Show - Channel 24 (Box 18)
    - N.A.E.A. - Conference - Philadelphia, 1970 (Box 18)
    - Create - Articles by E. Geiger (Box 18)
    - Press Releases and News Clippings (Box 18)
    - Speaking Appearances (P.A.S.T) (Box 18)
    - Peerless Camera - Camera Orders (Box 18)
    - American Film Institute (Box 18)
    - Shirley Kaplan Slide Presentation (Box 18)
    - Tom Spence Film - “Project Create Is” (Box 18)
    - Communicator’s Film - “It Was Worth Missing Recess” (Box 18)
    - Hartford Foundation (Box 18)
    - Move to 340 Capitol Avenue (Box 18)
    - Local Support - Solicitation, Offers, etc. (Box 18)
    - Letters of Support from Project Community Colleges, art galleries, etc. (Box 18)
    - Letters from School (Box 18)
    - “Project Create” - Directorship (Box 18)
    - U.S. Office of Education (Box 18)
    - Project Create - Original Manuscript (Box 18)
    - Master Copy - Application for Continuation Grant (Box 18)
    - Application for renewal, 1969-1970 (Box 18)
    - P.A.C.E. Manual (Box 18)
    - Rough Application for Renewal, 1969-1970 (Box 18)
    - Continuation Application Evaluation, 1969-1970 (Box 18)
    - Continuation Application Pt. I - Statistical, 1969-1970 (Box 18)
    - Continuation Application Pt. II - Narrative Report, 1969-1970 (Box 18)
    - Continuation Application Pt. III - Projected Activities, 1969-1970 (Box 18)
    - Continuation Application Pt. IV - Financial, 1969-1970 (Box 18)
    - Figures for Re-application Enrollment, breakdown of classes, races, population, etc. (Box 18)
    - Master for Create Final Report (Box 18)
    - Advisory Board (Box 18)
    - Planning Board Meeting (Box 18)
    - Directions to Hartford Insurance Group - Tower suite (Box 18)
    - Forms to reserve Conference Room to Wendy Backs, Higher Education (Box 18)
    - State Advisory Council - Title III (Box 18)
    - Create Consultants (Box 18)
    - Method of Selection and use of the Visiting Artist/ Consultant (Box 18)
    - Create Coordinators, 1969-1970 (Box 18)
    - Correspondence - Coordinators (Box 18)
    - Guest list - Project Schools (Box 18)
    - School Information, 1967-1968 (Box 18)
    - School Information, 1969-1970 (Box 18)
    - Direction to Project Schools (Box 18)
  - Chronological Correspondence Files - ASK and BKR. Files, 1967-1970 (Box 19)
    - Correspondence relating to orders (Box 19)
    - Create correspondence - chronological file, 1967-1968 (Box 19)
    - Create correspondence - chronological file, 1967-1968 (Box 19)
    - Create correspondence - chronological file, 1967-1968 (Box 19)
    - Create correspondence - chronological file, 1968-1969 (Box 19)
    - Create correspondence - chronological file, 1968-1969 (Box 19)
    - Create correspondence - chronological file, 1969-1970 (Box 19)
    - Title III - Project, Miscellaneous (Box 19)
    - Title III - Project, Miscellaneous (Box 19)
    - Create - New Theatrical Productions, etc. (Box 19)
    - Project E-1 (Title 3) (Box 19)
    - Insurance - Project Create (Box 19)
    - Project Suggestions - Theatre (Box 19)
    - Inquiries - Project Create - Miscellaneous (Box 19)
    - Project 3 - Proposal (Box 19)
    - Project Create - Titles III (Box 19)
    - Project Proposals (Box 19)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 19)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 19)
    - Create (Box 19)
    - Project Create (Box 19)
    - Minutes (Box 19)
    - BKR - phone calls (Box 19)
    - Project Create - Education Committee (Box 19)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 19)
  - Create Evaluation (Box 20)
    - Thomas Hooker School, Roger Williams School - Bridgeport (Box 20)
    - Groton Central Schools (Box 20)
    - Cornwall (Box 20)
    - Evaluation Responses, 1968-1969 (Box 20)
    - Pomfret (Box 20)
    - Waterbury (Box 20)
    - Hartford (Box 20)
    - Groton (Box 20)
    - Bristol (Box 20)
    - Questionnaires - Noble - Creat (Box 20)
    - Questionnaires - Pomfret (Box 20)
    - Questionnaires - Baldwin (Box 20)
    - Observers (Box 20)
    - Response Sheets (Box 20)
    - What I Like To Do (Box 20)
    - What I Like To Do (Box 20)
    - Baldwin School, Pomfret (Box 20)
    - Questionnaires, Hooker (Box 20)
    - Questionnaires, Cornwall (Box 20)
    - Questionnaires, Fisher (Box 20)
    - Evaluation: Procedures, Prospects, Plans (Box 20)
    - Evaluation: Questionnaires (Box 20)
    - Evaluation: Title III Advisory Committee’s Summary Evaluation (Box 20)
    - Evaluation: Comments (Box 20)
    - Evaluation, 1969-1970 (Box 20)
  - Correspondence Report (Box 21)
    - Education Writers and Editors (Box 21)
    - Connecticut Newspapers -Radio and TV Stations (Box 21)
    - Dickinson Associates (Box 21)
    - Children’s Theatre International, Inc. (Box 21)
    - Arts Publication - newsletters, magazine articles (Box 21)
    - Connecticut Education (Box 21)
    - Arts Education Project (Box 21)
    - Center for Arts Exposure, Inc. (Box 21)
    - Catalogue, CTB McGraw-Hill, 1970-1971 (Box 21)
    - Manual for Applicants and grantees (Box 21)
    - Southbury Project (Box 21)
    - Pact Preview, 1969 (Box 21)
    - Westchester Regional Education Center (Box 21)
    - Watercolor, Crayon Institute, Newtown, ct (Box 21)
    - Puerto Rico “Create” (Box 21)
    - Youth Film Council (Box 21)
    - Hartford (Box 21)
    - New Haven, Baldwin School (Box 21)
    - Pomfret (Box 21)
    - Waterbury (Box 21)
    - Consultant Form, 1969-1970 (Box 21)
    - Consultant Evaluation Form (Box 21)
    - Consultant List (Box 21)
    - Coordinators (Box 21)
    - Create Planning Board Meeting (Box 21)
    - Create Seminar III, 1969 (Box 21)
    - Children’s Theatre Conference (Box 21)
    - Letters (Box 21)
    - Workshop comments, feedback, 1967 September (Box 21)
    - Workshop O’Neill Memorial Theatre, 1967 September (Box 21)
    - In-school workshop attended, 1968 January-February (Box 21)
    - Workshop - participants’ biographies, 1967 December (Box 21)
    - September Seminar, River Edge, 1968 September (Box 21)
    - Workshop Program, rough copy, bio-info, 1968 (Box 21)
    - Introductory Seminar, 1969 September (Box 21)
    - Third Year Introductory Seminar prep. Material (cancelled) (Box 21)
    - Create Consultant Team- Master copy - selection and use (Box 21)
    - Production #2, second year, letter of interest (Box 21)
    - Hartt College of Music (Box 21)
    - Production #2, Second year proposal (Box 21)
    - The Little Sleep (Box 21)
    - Children’s Theatre International (Box 21)